Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Role-Playing Games, 1972-2009
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Modules, Manuals, and Campaign Volumes, 1973-2009 and undated, (2399 volumes)
  - RuneQuest
    - Rune Masters. Published by Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc., 1980., D04382314P (Box BG 39, Volume 659)
    - The Gateway Bestiary. Published by Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc., 1980., D04382313O (Box BG 39, Volume 658)
    - Cults of Terror: Nine Dangerous Deities for RuneQuest Role-Playing. Published by Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc., 1981., D04382308S (Box BG 39, Volume 651)
    - Griffin Mountain: A Complete Wilderness Campaign for RuneQuest. Published by Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc., 1981., D03574333S (Box BG 39, Volume 654)
    - Scorpion Hall: SoloQuest 2, 1st edition. Published by Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc., 1982., D04382629Y (Box BG 39, Volume 999)
    - SoloQuest: Three Solo Adventures. Published by Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc., 1982., D04382845Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1056)
    - The Snow King's Bride: SoloQuest 3, 1st edition. Published by Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc., 1982., D04382628X (Box BG 39, Volume 998)
    - RuneQuest Companion: History, Stories, and Play-Aids. Published by Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc., 1983., D04382309T (Box BG 39, Volume 652)
    - Apple Lane: Save the Hamlet from Scurrilous Scoundrels. Published by Baltimore, MD: The Avalon Hill Game Company, 1988., D04382305P (Box BG 39, Volume 648)
    - Gloranthan Bestiary: Creatures from Around the World. Published by Baltimore, MD: The Avalon Hill Game Company, 1988., D04382306Q (Box BG 39, Volume 649)
    - Into the Troll Realms: Troll Adventures and Encounters for RuneQuest. Published by Baltimore, MD: The Avalon Hill Game Company, 1988., D04382302M (Box BG 39, Volume 645)
    - RuneQuest Cities: Create and Explore Your Own Fantasy Communities. Published by Baltimore, MD: The Avalon Hill Game Company, 1988., D04382303N (Box BG 39, Volume 646)
    - Snake Pipe Hollows: Venture into the Heart of Chaos. Published by Baltimore, MD: The Avalon Hill Game Company, 1988., D04382304O (Box BG 39, Volume 647)
    - The Haunted Ruins: A Complete Troll Tribe for RuneQuest. Published by Baltimore, MD: The Avalon Hill Game Company, 1989., D04382301L (Box BG 39, Volume 644)
    - Daughters of Darkness and the Chronicles of Santon. Published by Baltimore, MD: The Avalon Hill Game Company, 1990., D04382307R (Box BG 39, Volume 650)
    - Eldarad: The Lost City. Published by Baltimore, MD: The Avalon Hill Game Company, 1990., D04382312N (Box BG 39, Volume 657)
    - River of Cradles: Lands and Peoples of Pavis and the Zola Fel Valley. Published by Baltimore, MD: The Avalon Hill Game Company, 1992., D03574334T (Box BG 39, Volume 643)
    - Sun County. Published by Baltimore, MD: The Avalon Hill Game Company, 1992., D03574340Q (Box BG 39, Volume 636)
    - Dorastor: Land of Doom. Published by Baltimore, MD: The Avalon Hill Game Company, 1993., D04382298- (Box BG 39, Volume 634)
    - RuneQuest: Deluxe Edition. Published by Baltimore, MD: The Avalon Hill Game Company, 1993., D03574341R (Box BG 39, Volume 633)
    - Shadows on the Borderland. Published by Baltimore, MD: The Avalon Hill Game Company, 1993., D04382299. (Box BG 39, Volume 635)
    - Lords of Terror: The Cults of Dorastor. Published by Baltimore, MD: The Avalon Hill Game Company, 1994., D04382296Y (Box BG 39, Volume 631)
    - Strangers in Prax. Published by Baltimore, MD: The Avalon Hill Game Company, 1994., D04382297Z (Box BG 39, Volume 632)
  - Shadowrun
    - DNA/DOA. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1989., D04563713T (Box BG 39, Volume 1986)
    - Dreamchipper. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1989., D04563711R (Box BG 39, Volume 1984)
    - Mercurial: In Concert at Underworld. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1989., D04563712S (Box BG 39, Volume 1985)
    - Shadowrun: Where Man Meets Magic and Machine. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1989., D04400515J (Box BG 39, Volume 1973)
    - Silver Angel. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1989., D04405970T (Box BG 39, Volume M6)
    - Sprawl Sites. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1989., D04400516K (Box BG 39, Volume 1972)
    - Street Samurai Catalog. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1989., D04400517L (Box BG 39, Volume 1971)
    - Bottled Demon. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1990., D04563709Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1982)
    - Harlequin. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1990., D04563708X (Box BG 39, Volume 1981)
    - Paranormal Animals of North America. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1990., D04400518M (Box BG 39, Volume 1970)
    - Queen Euphoria. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1990., D04563710Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1983)
    - Seattle Sourcebook. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1990., D04563698+ (Box BG 39, Volume 1963)
    - The Grimoire. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1990., D04563704T (Box BG 39, Volume 1969)
    - The Neo-Anarchist's Guide to North America. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1990., D04563694. (Box BG 39, Volume 1959)
    - The Universal Brotherhood. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1990., D04563681X (Box BG 39, Volume 1960)
    - Dragon Hunt. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1991., D04563707W (Box BG 39, Volume 1980)
    - Elven Fire. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1991., D04400511F (Box BG 39, Volume 1977)
    - Ivy and Chrome. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1991., D04400512G (Box BG 39, Volume 1976)
    - London Sourcebook. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1991., D04563695 (Box BG 39, Volume 1961)
    - Native American Nations, Vol. 1. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1991., D04563697/ (Box BG 39, Volume 1962)
    - Native American Nations, Vol. 2. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1991., D04563675- (Box BG 39, Volume 1958)
    - Rigger Black Book. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1991., D04563702R (Box BG 39, Volume 1967)
    - Total Eclipse. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1991., D04563706V (Box BG 39, Volume 1979)
    - Virtual Realities. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1991., D04563703S (Box BG 39, Volume 1968)
    - Contacts. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1992., D04405970T (Box BG 39, Volume M6)
    - Imago. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1992., D04563705U (Box BG 39, Volume 1978)
    - One Stage Before. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1992., D04400513H (Box BG 39, Volume 1975)
    - Shadowbeat. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1992., D04563701Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1966)
    - Shadowrun, Second Edition (#7900). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1992., D04563964. (Box BG 39, Volume 2218)
    - ShadowTech. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1992., D04563700P (Box BG 39, Volume 1965)
    - Street Samurai Catalog (#7104). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1992., D04563963- (Box BG 39, Volume 2217)
    - The Grimoire (#7903). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1992., D04563958/ (Box BG 39, Volume 2212)
    - The Neo-Anarchists' Guide to Real Life. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1992., D04563676. (Box BG 39, Volume 1956)
    - A Killing Glare (#7314). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1993., D04563981- (Box BG 39, Volume 2235)
    - Celtic Double-Cross (#7315). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1993., D04563980Z (Box BG 39, Volume 2234)
    - Corporate Shadowfiles: A Shadowrun Sourcebook (#7113). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1993., D04563971Z (Box BG 39, Volume 2225)
    - Dark Angel. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1993., D04400514I (Box BG 39, Volume 1974)
    - Germany Sourcebook (#7204). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1993., D04563975$ (Box BG 39, Volume 2229)
    - Paranormal Animals of Europe. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1993., D04563699% (Box BG 39, Volume 1964)
    - Tir Na Nog (#7211). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1993., D04563972- (Box BG 39, Volume 2226)
    - Tir Tairngire (#7210). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1993., D04563973. (Box BG 39, Volume 2227)
    - Divided Assets (#7318). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1994., D04563978% (Box BG 39, Volume 2232)
    - Double Exposure: A Shadowrun Adventure (#7319). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1994., D04563977+ (Box BG 39, Volume 2231)
    - Eye Witness (#7316). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1994., D045639790 (Box BG 39, Volume 2233)
    - Fields of Fire (#7114). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1994., D04563970Y (Box BG 39, Volume 2224)
    - Harlequin's Back (#7320). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1994., D04563976/ (Box BG 39, Volume 2230)
    - Lone Star (#7115). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1994., D04563969% (Box BG 39, Volume 2223)
    - Paradise Lost (#7317). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1994., D04563974 (Box BG 39, Volume 2228)
    - Prime Runners: A Shadowrun Sourcebook (#7116). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1994., D04563968+ (Box BG 39, Volume 2222)
    - Sprawl Maps. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1994., D04563680W (Box BG 39, Volume 1957)
    - Awakenings: New Magic in 2057 (#7120). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1995., D04563957$ (Box BG 39, Volume 2211)
    - Aztlan: A Shadowrun Sourcebook (#7213). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1995., D04563966$ (Box BG 39, Volume 2220)
    - Bug City (#7117). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1995., D04563962Z (Box BG 39, Volume 2216)
    - Corporate Security Handbook (#7118). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1995., D04563967/ (Box BG 39, Volume 2221)
    - Cybertechnology: A Shadowrun Sourcebook (#7119). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1995., D04563965 (Box BG 39, Volume 2219)
    - Virtual Realities 2.0: A Shadowrun Sourcebook (#7904). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1995., D04563956 (Box BG 39, Volume 2210)
    - California: Free State (#7209). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1996., D04563955. (Box BG 39, Volume 2209)
    - Portfolio of a Dragon: Dunkelzahn's Secrets (#7122). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1996., D04563961Y (Box BG 39, Volume 2215)
    - Shadowrun Companion: Beyond the Shadows (#7905). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1996., D04563952Y (Box BG 39, Volume 2206)
    - Shadows of the Underworld (#7323). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1996., D04563959+ (Box BG 39, Volume 2213)
    - Super Tuesday! (#7322). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1996., D04563960X (Box BG 39, Volume 2214)
    - Threats (#7121). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1996., D04563954- (Box BG 39, Volume 2208)
    - Cyberpirates!. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1997., D04563735X (Box BG 39, Volume 2008)
    - Missions. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1997., D04563740T (Box BG 39, Volume 2013)
    - Mob War!. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1997., D04563742V (Box BG 39, Volume 2015)
    - Rigger 2. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1997., D04563741U (Box BG 39, Volume 2014)
    - Target: UCAS (#7214). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1997., D04563953Z (Box BG 39, Volume 2207)
    - Underworld Sourcebook. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1997., D04563743W (Box BG 39, Volume 2016)
    - Blood in the Boardroom. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1998., D04563739. (Box BG 39, Volume 2012)
    - Critters. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1998., D04403689Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1519)
    - Critters. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1998., D04405970T (Box BG 39, Volume M6)
    - Predator and Prey. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1998., D04563737Z (Box BG 39, Volume 2010)
    - Renraku Arcology Shutdown. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1998., D04563736Y (Box BG 39, Volume 2009)
    - Shadowrun, 3rd edition. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1998., D04254496Y (Box BG 39, Volume 44)
    - Shadowrun, 3rd. Edition. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1998., D04403706O (Box BG 39, Volume 1520)
    - Shadowrun, 3rd. Edition. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1998., D04563734W (Box BG 39, Volume 2007)
    - Target: Smuggler Havens. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1998., D04563738- (Box BG 39, Volume 2011)
    - Corporate Download. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1999., D04563730S (Box BG 39, Volume 2003)
    - First Run. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1999., D04563733V (Box BG 39, Volume 2006)
    - Magic in the Shadows. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1999., D04563731T (Box BG 39, Volume 2004)
    - Man and Machine: Cyberware. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1999., D04563725W (Box BG 39, Volume 1998)
    - New Seattle. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1999., D04403716P (Box BG 39, Volume 1605)
    - Shadowrun Companion. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1999., D04563732U (Box BG 39, Volume 2005)
    - Shadowrun: Quick Start Rules. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1999., D04563727Y (Box BG 39, Volume 2000)
    - Brainscan. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 2000., D04563726X (Box BG 39, Volume 1999)
    - Cannon Companion. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 2000., D04563723U (Box BG 39, Volume 1996)
    - Corporate Punishment. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 2000., D04563728Z (Box BG 39, Volume 2001)
    - Matrix. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 2000., D04563722T (Box BG 39, Volume 1995)
    - Target: Matrix. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 2000., D04563721S (Box BG 39, Volume 1994)
    - New Seattle. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2001., D04563729- (Box BG 39, Volume 2002)
    - Rigger 3. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 2001., D04563724V (Box BG 39, Volume 1997)
    - Target: Awakened Lands. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2001., D04563720R (Box BG 39, Volume 1993)
    - Year of the Comet. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2001., D04563715V (Box BG 39, Volume 1988)
    - Shadows of North America. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2002., D04563718Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1991)
    - State of the Art: 2063. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2002., D04563716W (Box BG 39, Volume 1989)
    - Survival of the Fittest. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2002., D04564026R (Box BG 39, Volume 2295)
    - Target: Wastelands. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2002., D04563717X (Box BG 39, Volume 1990)
    - Threats 2. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2002., D04563719Z (Box BG 39, Volume 1992)
    - Wake of the Comet. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2002., D04563714U (Box BG 39, Volume 1987)
    - Cannon Companion. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2003., D04564029U (Box BG 39, Volume 2299)
    - Character Dossier. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2003., D04563896+ (Box BG 39, Volume 2298)
    - Dragons of the Sixth World. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2003., D04564027S (Box BG 39, Volume 2296)
    - Sprawl Survival Guide. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2003., D04564028T (Box BG 39, Volume 2297)
    - Mr. Johnson's Little Black Book. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2004., D04564025Q (Box BG 39, Volume 2294)
    - Shadows of Europe. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2004., D04564024P (Box BG 39, Volume 2293)
    - State of the Art: 2064. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2004., D04564023O (Box BG 39, Volume 2292)
    - Loose Alliances. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2005., D04564022N (Box BG 39, Volume 2291)
    - Shadowrun, 4th ed.. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2005., D04564021M (Box BG 39, Volume 2290)
    - Shadows of Asia. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2005., D04564017R (Box BG 39, Volume 2285)
    - System Failure. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2005., D04564016Q (Box BG 39, Volume 2284)
    - On the Run. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2006., D04564018S (Box BG 39, Volume 2287)
    - Runner Havens. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2006., D04564020L (Box BG 39, Volume 2289)
    - Shadowrun: Gamemaster's Screen, 4th ed.. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2006., D04563895/ (Box BG 39, Volume 2286)
    - Street Magic. Published by Chicago, IL: FanPro LLC, 2006., D04564019T (Box BG 39, Volume 2288)
    - Quick-Start Rules. Published by WizKids, Inc. (Catalyst Game Labs), undated., D04405970T (Box BG 39, Volume M6)
  - Sherlock Holmes
    - Sherlock Holmes Consulting Detective. Published by San Francisco, CA: Sleuth Publications Ltd., 1981., D04405649W (Box BG 39, Volume M3)
    - The Mansion Murders, Vol. II. Published by San Francisco, CA: Sleuth Publications, Ltd., 1983., D04403820L (Box BG 39, Volume 1638)
    - The Queen's Park Affair, Vol. III. Published by San Francisco, CA: Sleuth Publications Ltd., 1984., D04405648V (Box BG 39, Volume M4)
  - Space Master
    - Action on Akaisha Outstation. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1985., D04383041N (Box BG 39, Volume 1368)
    - Imperial Crisis: House Devon in Turmoil. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1985., D04383034P (Box BG 39, Volume 1361)
    - Lost Telepaths: The Secret of House Kashmere. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1986., D04383033O (Box BG 39, Volume 1360)
    - Beyond the Core: The Worlds of Frontier Zone Five. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1987., D04383032N (Box BG 39, Volume 1359)
    - The Cygnus Conspiracy: A Subject World Plots Revolt!. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1987., D04383040M (Box BG 39, Volume 1367)
    - League of Merchants: Lords of the Imperial Underworld. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1988., D04382715U (Box BG 39, Volume 1353)
    - Tales from Deep Space: Perils on the Imperial Frontier. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1988., D04383039U (Box BG 39, Volume 1366)
    - War on a Distant Moon: The Tayan Revolution. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1988., D04383038T (Box BG 39, Volume 1365)
    - Disaster on Adanis III. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1989., D04383035Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1362)
    - Legacy of the Ancients: Survivors of a Forgotten Colony Ship. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1989., D04383036R (Box BG 39, Volume 1363)
    - Raiders from the Frontier: House Jade-London Besieged. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1989., D04383029T (Box BG 39, Volume 1354)
    - The Durandrium Find: Salvation for House Augustus-Hayes. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1989., D04383037S (Box BG 39, Volume 1364)
  - Space Opera
    - Ground and Air Equipment. Published by Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1981., D04382660T (Box BG 39, Volume 1055)
    - Seldon's Compendium of Starcraft I. Published by Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1981., D04382661U (Box BG 39, Volume 1054)
    - Incedus III. Published by Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1982., D04382710P (Box BG 39, Volume 1053)
    - Agents of Rebellion. Published by Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1983., D04382709X (Box BG 39, Volume 1052)
  - Spell Jammer
    - Casino Galactica. Published by Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1983., D04382708W (Box BG 39, Volume 1051)
    - Crystal Spheres. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04382229U (Box BG 39, Volume 512)
    - Lost Ships. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04382291T (Box BG 39, Volume 625)
    - Monstrous Compendium: Appendix. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04382447W (Box BG 39, Volume 819)
    - Skull and Crossbows. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04382230M (Box BG 39, Volume 513)
    - Wildspace. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04382231N (Box BG 39, Volume 514)
    - Dungeon Master's Screen. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1991., D04382289- (Box BG 39, Volume 623)
    - Goblin's Return. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1991., D04382227S (Box BG 39, Volume 510)
    - Monstrous Compendium: Appendix. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1991., D04382448X (Box BG 39, Volume 820)
    - Practical Planetology. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1991., D04382288Z (Box BG 39, Volume 622)
    - Realmspace. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1991., D04382290S (Box BG 39, Volume 624)
    - Under the Dark Fist. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1991., D04382228T (Box BG 39, Volume 511)
    - Greyspace. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D04382286X (Box BG 39, Volume 620)
    - Heart of the Enemy. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D04382226R (Box BG 39, Volume 509)
    - Rock of Bral. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D04382287Y (Box BG 39, Volume 621)
    - The Complete Spacefarer's Handbook. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D03805795. (Box BG 39, Volume 508)
    - Krynnspace. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1993., D04382284V (Box BG 39, Volume 616)
    - Space Lairs. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1993., D04382232O (Box BG 39, Volume 515)
  - Stalking the Night
    - Stalking the Night Fantastic. Published by Madison Hts, MI: Tri Tac, Inc., 1983., D04403817R (Box BG 39, Volume 1658)
    - Hellsnight: A City Dies at Midnight. Published by Madison Hts, MI: Tri Tac, Inc., 1988., D04403773S (Box BG 39, Volume 1586)
  - Star Drive
    - Alien Compendium. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1998., D04382685- (Box BG 39, Volume 1045)
    - Arms and Equipment Guide. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1998., D04382686. (Box BG 39, Volume 1044)
    - Black Starfall. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1998., D04382664X (Box BG 39, Volume 1040)
    - Red Starrise. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1998., D04382665Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1039)
    - The Last Warhulk. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1998., D04382663W (Box BG 39, Volume 1041)
    - The Lighthouse. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1998., D04382666Z (Box BG 39, Volume 1038)
    - Outbound, an Explorer's Guidebook. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1999., D04382683Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1047)
    - Planet of Darkness. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1999., D04382662V (Box BG 39, Volume 1042)
    - Star Compendium. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1999., D04382681W (Box BG 39, Volume 1049)
    - Stardrive: Campaign Setting. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1999., D04382680V (Box BG 39, Volume 1050)
    - Threats from Beyond. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1999., D04382682X (Box BG 39, Volume 1048)
    - Alien Compendium 2: Exploration of 2503. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 2000., D04382684Z (Box BG 39, Volume 1046)
    - System Guide to Aegis. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 2000., D04382696 (Box BG 39, Volume 1043)
  - Star Frontiers
    - Starspwan of Volturnus. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1982., D04382204N (Box BG 39, Volume 462)
    - Volturnus, Planet of Mystery. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1982., D04382203M (Box BG 39, Volume 463)
    - Referee's Screen and Mini-Module. Published by TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1983., D04382202L (Box BG 39, Volume 464)
    - Sundown on Starmist. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1983., D04382197Y (Box BG 39, Volume 461)
    - 2001 a Space Odyssey. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1984., D04382192T (Box BG 39, Volume 470)